Preliminary Inventory to the Carla A. Hills Papers, 1964-1993
Hoover Institution Archives
- G. New York Housing Authority Administrative Loan
- H. New York City Housing Authority (NYCAA) Operating Subsidy
- I. No-Fault Insurance
- J. Nuclear Energy
- K. Stregnthening Public Management in the Intergovermental System, Report by Study Committee on Policy Management Assistance
- L. Organization/Management Activities Report to Congress by Secretary of HUD, March 1976
- A. Wage & Price Standards (Fast Book) (Box 228-231)
- B. Urban Policy
- C. Urban Jobs & Enterprise Zone
- D. UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA
- E. Supreme Court Clerks
- F. Stanford University (Exec. Program in the Humanities)
- G. Statements, thru __________ Vol. #5, 1980
- H. Society for Promoting Useful Knowledge
- I. Jennifer Jones Simon Foundation for Mental Health & Education
- J. Standing Committee on Specialization
- K. Section of Legal Education & Admissions to the Bar
- L. Section of Corporation, Banking & Business Law
- M. ABA Commission on Evaluation of Professional Standards
- N. Task Force on Professional Competence
- O. ABA Special Committee on Antitrust Penalties & Damages
- P. Uniform Law on Notarial Acts
- Q. ABA Section of Corporation, Banking & Business Law
- R. ABA Standing Committee on Professional Discipline
- S. Reports of Committees of the House of Delegates
- T. American Bar Association
- U. Fellows, American Bar Association
- V. American Law Institute
- W. VICTORY, 1980
- X. Harry Walker, Inc.
- Y. West Coast University
- Z. Welfare Reform
- AA. Welfare Legislation
- BB. Washington Metropolitan Area Corporate Counsel Assn., 6/16/81
- "Special Committee on the Tort Liability System"
- A. Kenneth T. Rosen (Box 232-234)
- B. Republican Congressional Committee
- C. Library of Congress
- D. Lincoln Institute
- E. Legal Aid Society
- F. Legal Counsel For the Elderly
- G. Law Review Articles - Miscellaneous
- H. Law Students in Court
- I. Kraft Inc.
- J. Korn/Perry International
- K. Kimberly Clark Corporation
- L. Charles J. Kelly Jr. (Commonwealth Communications)
- M. PRESIDENT'S COMMITTEE Interim Report, URBAN DEVELOPMENT/NEIGHBORHOOD REVITALIZATION
- N. RMH 50th Suprise Party
- O. Percy, Senator Charles H.
- P. Panama Canal
- Q. Dean L. Overman
- R. Olivetti Corporation of America re Silver Seiko
- S. Japanese Companies
- T. Investor Responsibility Research Center
- U. Intraband Competition
- V. International Foundation for Cultural Cooperation/Development
- W. Olympic Committee re Coin Program Proposal
- X. Otis Art Institute of Los Angeles/Parsons School of Design in New York - Honorary Committee
- Y. Occidental College - Bond Question
- Z. Nucorp, Inc.
- AA. Los Angeles League of Women Voters
- BB. Los Angeles County Bar Association
- CC. Latham & Watkins Partnership Meeting, 3/20/81
- DD. Knox Dinner Party
- EE. International Executive Service Corps
- FF. Lawyers Committee For Civil Rights Under the Law
- CARLA A. HILLS (Box 234-243)
- President's Commission on Housing
- Munger tolles files on anti trust + UCLA TEACHING MATERIALS (Box 243-245)
- ADMINISTRATIVE CONFERENCE OF THE UNITED STATES, 1973-1973 (Box 246-247)
- A. §8 Existing Reconnassaince Study (Box 248-250)
- B. Selected Citites: Data Book U.S. Conference of Mayors Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 6/26-30/76
- C. FY 78 Budget Press Briefing Questions & Answers
- D. HUD Budget FY 79
- E. Capital Markets and the Housing Sector Study
- A. ASE - Correspondence vol #5, Septe,ber, 1978 - February, 1979 (Box 252-254)
- B. ASE - Correspondence vol #4, June, 1978 - August, 1978
- C. ASE - Correspondence vol #3, March, 1978 - May, 1978
- D. ASE Correspondence vol #2, October, 1977 - February, 1978
- E. ASE Correspondence vol #1
- F. ASE Business Council
- G. ASE Ad Council
- H. ASE Farm Line
- I. ASE Editor Letters
- J. ASE Fortune 500
- K. ASE Disney Productions
- L. ASE - International Trade Mart
- M. ASE - American Assembly
- N. ASE - Objecitme Analysis of House - Passed National Energy Act
- O. ASE - National Town Meeting Program
- P. ASE - Board of Directors
- Q. ASE - Board of Directors Meeting, 7/29/77
- R. ASE - Minutes of the First Board of Directors Meeting, 4/1/77
- S. ASE - Board of Advisors
- T. ASE - Board of Advisors, Minutes of First Meeting, 5/26/77
- U. ASE - Advisory Board, U.S. Senators
- V. ASE - Advisory Board, House of Representatives
- W. ASE - Development Associates Brakeley, John Price Jones Correspondence
- X. ASE - Contract with Development Associates
- Y. Acknowledgement Letters to respondent's First Wave Letters, 5/6/77
- Z. Preliminary Report of Fund - Raising Consultant 6/6/77 Meeting
- aa. ASE - Executive Committee
- bb. ASE - Finance Development Committee
- cc. Agriculture Committee Corr.
- dd. Commercial Committee Corr.
- ee. Communication Committee Corr.
- ff. Education Committee Corr.
- gg. Industrial Committee Corr.
- hh. Membership Committee Corr.
- ii. Residential Committee Corr.
- jj. Transportation Committee Corr.
- kk. Weekly Reports to Senator Percy
- ll. ASE Percy's Staff Listing
- mm. ASE New York State Alliance
- nn. ASE Wisconsin State Alliance
- oo. Illinois State Alliance Corr.
- pp. ASE State Energy Offices
- qq. ASE Congressional Energy Offices
- rr. ASE - Trade Association Listings
- ss. ASE - Pokeny, Gene Ca,bridge Reports, Inc.
- tt. ASE - J. Walter Thompson Company
- uu. ASE - Edisnon Electric Institute
- vv. ASE - Miscellanwous
- ww. ASE - Resumes
- xx. Professional Appoitment Book, 1976
- yy. Week-at-a-Glance Business Reminder, 1975
- Carter Transition (Carter Urban Statement) (Box 255-257)
- Urban Material (Ford Urban Report, RNC Urban Pamphlet)
- STANDARDS OF CONDUCT - Gifts and Gratuities from
- Contractors to Federal Employees
- Conflict of Interest
- LATHAM, WATKINS & HILLS - Congratulatory Letters
- African Development Group
- CITIES/PEOPLE IN DISTRESS - Draft
- Congressional Hearings By CAH
- Antitrust Regulation of Insurance
- A COMPARATIVE ANALYSIS OF SUBSIDIZED HOUSING COSTS, 7/28/76
- Community Development Bank
- CBDG - Brookings Study of the CDBG Allocation Formula
- AIRLIE HOUSE MEETING re Conference on Department Management
- Budget FY 78 (HUD)
- Correspondence Flow
- Improvements Needed in the Formula Used to Allocate CBDG Funds
- GAO Draft Rpt. -, 5/24/76
- CBDG - New CBDG Formula
- CBDG - Miscellaneous
- CBDG EVALUATION - Study by LBJ School of Public Affairs
- A. Detroit, (April, 1975) (Box 257-259)
- B. Counseling for Delinquent Mortgagers II, A Staff Study
- C. Council On International Economic Policy
- D. Emergency Homeowner's Relief Act - First Report to Congress, 8/29/75
- E. Economic Policy Board - Report for the Quarterly Domestic Economic Review, 2nd Quarter, 1975 (7/25/75)
- F. Energy - General
- G. National Program for Solar Heating and Cooling, 1/9/76
- H. Energy Conservation Legislation
- I. Experimental Housing Allowance Program (EHAP), 11/29/76
- J. Evaluation, A Forum for Human Service Decision Makers Vol. 3, Nos. 1-2, 1976
- K. Evaluation of The Effectiveness of Congregate Housing For The Elderly
- L. Monthly Reports By The Field
- M. Memorandum re Realignment of Field Office Responsibilities
- N. Experimental Housing Allowance Program
- O. EXPECTED TO RESIDE - Needs of The Central Cities
- P. Executive Interchange Program
- Q. Housing and Planning References - November/December, 1976
- R. HUD Challenge, Special HUD Awards Issue, January, 1977
- S. Future Role Of FHA, 12/31/76
- T. Fundamental Changes Are Needed In Federal Assistance To State/Local Governments GAO Rpt., 8/19/75
- U. Housing Block Grant Proposal
- V. OPERATION BREAKTHROUGH - Lessons Learned About Demonstrating New Technology, GAO Draft Rpt., 7/28/76
- W. National Urban Beautification Systems
- X. MEASURE OF POVERTY
- Z. International Economic Report Of The President, January 1977
- AA. NATIONAL STANDARDS NEEDED FOR RESIDENTIAL ENERGY CONSERVATION - Comptroller General Report, 6/20/75
- A. The Attorney General's Advocacy Institute (Box 260-261)
- B. Strategy for Providing Assistance to the Poor
- C. Administrative Conference of the United States Mtg., MAR 23
- D. Department of Justice Authorization and Oversight, 1981
- E. Sloan Commission
- A. President Ford's '76 Factbook (Box 262-264)
- B. Carter Quote Book
- C. Carla A. Hills Blue Binder, (2 Binders)
- D. President Ford's Committee Advocate's Briefing Book
- E. PFC Working and Traveling Briefing Binder
- F. President Ford's '76 Factbook
- G. Democratic/Republican Statements (folder)
- H. U.S. News & World Report, August 30, 1976
- CAHills (Box 265-266)
  - 1) Alliance to Save Energy
  - 2) ABA Task Force on Judicial Compensation
  - 3) ABA - Special Committee on Tort Liability System
- Private Sector Advisory Panel on Infrastructure Financing
- Carla A. Hills (Box 266-269)
- ABA - Meeting Notebooks -, 1981-82
- Antitrust Developments, Second
- ABA (Box 269-271)
  - Spring Meeting, 1983
  - Midwinter Meeting, 1983
  - FTC Articles
  - 1982 Committee Appointments
  - Compendium of Foreign Laws & Regulations Affecting International Franchising
  - Congratulations on Election as Section Chairman
  - Washington Office Laison
  - Lawyers Title Guaranty Funds (Newsletter)
  - Legal Assistance Newsletter
  - Proposed Merger Guidelines
  - Miscellaneous Requests for Blanket Authority
  - Oversight Hearings on Antitrust Laws
  - Contribution Legislation
  - Antitrust Division/Dept. of Justice
- AMERICAN BAR ASSOCIATION (Box 272-274)
  - Antitrust Section 1982 Spring Meeting
  - David Bickel Article
  - 1983 Midyear Meeting/Reports
  - Drafts - Model Standards for Specialization
  - Petroleum Marketing Attorneys - Meeting, 1983
  - Litigation Section's Comments on ALI Corporate Governance Project
  - ABA - General Correspondence, Board of Governors Reports, Etc.
- Trilateral Commission Publications (Box 274-276)
- Trilateral Commission Publications & Correspondence thru, 1982
- Urban Institute Board of Trustees, October 16, 1981
- Urban Institute - Correspondence, March 1980-February 1982
- MISCELLANEOUS (Box 276-277)
  - President's Commission on Housing
  - Norton Simon Museum
  - Overseas Education Fund
  - Victor Palmieri
  - Pepperdine University
  - Puerto Rico
  - Republican State Central Committee on California
  - Republican Womens Task force
  - Youth Orchestra
  - Roseborough Monument Co. v. Memorial Park Cemetary Assn.
  - Schools - Sidwell, Potomac
  - School Prayer
  - Volunteer Organizations
  - Vermillion
  - Ralph C. Sutro Company
- Carla A. Hills (Box 279-281)
- ABA Antitrust Section, 1982-1983
- Antitrust Section 1983 - Annual/Post Annual Meeting (Box 282-284)
- Antitrust Section - Fall Council Meeting -, 1983
- Annual Meeting - Council Agenda, 1983
- Annual Meeting - Delegate Issues, 1983
- ABA - 1983 Annual Meeting -- Atlanta
- Contribution Monograph
- Criminal A/T Jury Instructions
- Blanket Authority Handbook
- Use of Economists in Antitrust Litigation
- National Court of Appeals
- 1982 Conference of § Chairman
- 1983 Committee Materials
- 1983 General Correspondence
- 1. LW&H DC office structure announcement (Box 284-286)
- 2. CAH master list, 2/2/81
- 3. Alliance To Save Energy publications
- 4. Alliance To Save Energy annual meeting, 3/10/83
- 5. Alliance To Save Energy policy directions, '80-'81
- 6. Alliance To Save Energy Executive Committee and Board of Directors meetings, 9/16/82
- 7. Alliance To Save Energy annual meeting, 3/22/84
- 8. Alliance To Save Energy, 9/81-4/84
- 9. Alliance To Save Energy report and financial statements, 12/31/80 and 1979
- 10. Alliance To Save Energy roster
- 11. Smithsorian Institution National Associates Board
- 12. [UNK] Program -- Tokyo, Japan, May 1984
- 1. International Executive Service Corps (Box 286-288)
- 2. Hinson
- 3. Kettering Foundation
- 4. Independent Refiners Assn of California
- 5. Housing Roundtable, (1982)
- 6. HUD presentation at Fair Housing Week ceremonies, 4/2/84
- 7. Housing: Mortgage Revenue Bonds
- 8. Housing Development Reporter -- Editorial Advisory Board
- 9. Hoover Institution (CAH papers), Stanford University
- 10. National Assn of Home Builders
- 11. National Assn of Former U.S. Attorneys
- 12. National Institute of Building Sciences
- 13. Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law, Vol I
- 14. Corporate Counsel Institute -- Correspondence
- 15. White House Conference on Productivity, 1982-83
- 16. Fair Housing
- 17. Harvard Business School Board of Visitors
- 18. MIT/Harvard Joint Center for Urban Studies -- Advisory Committee
- 19. American Medical Record Assn
- CARLA A. HILLS (Box 288-291)
- American Bar Association - Special
- Committee on the Tort Liability System
- AMERICAN BAR ASSOCIATION
  - Special Committee to Study Antitrust Remedies
  - Blanket Authority Coordination Proposal
  - ANttRUST SECTION - Corporate Counsel Task Force
  - ANttRUST SECTION - Revisions to Manual for Complex Litigation
  - Long Range Planning Committee
  - Conference of Section Chairmen
  - Beckham Amendment
  - ABA Annual Meeting, 1984
  - ANttRUST SECTION - Illinois Brick Task Force
  - 1984 General Correspondence ANttRUST SECTION
  - Conference of Section Chairman - Correspondence, 12/2/83 - 6/21/84
  - Conference of Section Chairman - Correspondence, 6/29/84 - 7/13/84
  - Task Force on Proposed Antitrust Legislation
  - Invitations - ABA Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 291-294)
- AMERICAN BAR ASSOCIATION (Box 294-296)
  - National Institutes Committee
  - ABA - Washington Letter
  - ABA - Washington Summary
  - ABA - Antitrust Section Committee Agendas, 1983 - 1984
  - ABA SECTION OF ANttRUST LAW Council Meetings WESTIN HOTEL, Chicago, IL, 8/5/84
  - Antitrust Dection - Midwinter Meeting - Cerromar -, Jan. '84
  - ABA SECTION OF ANttRUST LAW 32nd Annual Spring Meeting SHOREHAM HOTEL, 3/21/84
- URBAN INSttUTE - Notebooks, Board Meetings of APR & OCT of 1983 (Box 296-298)
  - - Executive Committee (Notebooks) of: JUL, OCT, DEC 1983
- American Council for Capital Formation, Correspondence, MAR 1978 - AUG 83
- American Council on Capital Formation - Newsletters
- Point Paper Re Watts Neighborhood Shopping Center, 2/24/84
- Academy for State & Local Government
- Lake City Associates
- American Council On Capital Formation - Fundraising Information
- BROOKINGS INSttUTION - Bulletins, 1976 - 1982
- CAHills (Box 299)
- American Bar Association
- Antitrust Section
- 1982 Meetings
- Alliance to Save Energy (Box 300-302)
- American Council for Capital Formation
- Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law
- Mott Foundation Study
- Peterson Budget Group
- Senate Briefing Book: Super 301 statute, (1989) (Box 304)
- Labor Advisory Committee Briefing Book, (1989)
- Japan Trip 1989 Briefing Book and Agenda
- Quadrilateral Meeting of Trade Ministers, Japan, 1989 (Box 305)
- Europe Briefing Book and Agenda, (1989)
- Materials on Paris Summit, (1989)
- Briefing on National Trade Estimates Report for Finance Committee Special 301 Materials (Box 306)
- Briefing Ways and Means on Super/Special 301, (1990)
- Materials for Press Briefing: Super/Special/Title VII, (1989)
- Briefing of House Judiciary Committee on IPR (Box 307)
- State of the Union, 1990
- Consumers for World Trade Award Dinner, (1991)
- Legislative Reports to Hills, (1989-92)
- Misc. Press Releases (Box 308)
- 1988 Transition Briefing Book
- File on Who's Who Publications (Box 309)
- Congratulatory Letters, (1988-89) (Box 309-310)
- Clippings on RMH (Box 311)
- Clippings on CAH
- Invitations (accepted & declined), 1989-1993 (Box 312-323)
- CAH PERSONAL FILES
  - Rep Funds (Box 323)
  - CAH Diner's Club Account (closed out 3/92)
  - Postage Expenses
  - White House Mess reimbursements (Box 324)
  - Daily Schedules, 1989-1992/3 (Box 324-5)
  - Telephone Log, 1989-1992/3 (Box 325-6)
- CAH PERSONAL FILES - TRAVEL
  - Travel Vouchers, 1989-1992/3 (Box 326-329)
- Bork Nomination Files (Box 330-332)
  - Bork Nomination Files